let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Also called Rajarajeswaram, it is a Hindu temple dedicated to Shiva located in South bank of Cauvery river in Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu. Can you recognize this famous monument?",
    answer: "Brihadeeswarar Temple",
    options: [
      "Thrikkakudi Rock-Cut Temple",
      "Brihadeeswarar Temple",
      "Veerbhadra Temple",
      "Thousand Pillar Temple"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not true about Somnath temple?",
    answer: "Somnath means “The Lord of the Sun,” which is one of the names of Lord Shiva.",
    options: [
      "The Somnath temple is located in Veraval in Gujarat.",
      "Somnath means “The Lord of the Sun,” which is one of the names of Lord Shiva.",
      "The temple is built in Chalukya style of temple architecture and is made of sandstones.",
      "The temple is seven-storied and 155 feet tall."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It is a historical palace and the royal residence in Karnataka. It is now one of the most famous tourist attractions in India, after the Taj Mahal. Can you recognize this magnificent palace?",
    answer: "Mysore Palace",
    options: [
      "Mysore Palace",
      "Bangalore Palace",
      "Seshadri Iyer Memorial",
      "Chaturmukha Basadi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Uttarakhand famously known as Devbhumi has so many remarkable monuments. Can you guess which of these monuments is located in Uttarakhand?",
    answer: "Badrinath Temple",
    options: [
      "Badrinath Temple",
      "Rock Cut Temple",
      "Rang Ghar",
      "Gol Gumbaz"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "This monument is often referred to as the 'Colosseum of the East'. Can you guess this monument?",
    answer: "Rang Ghar",
    options: [
      "Talatal Ghar",
      "Siddheshwar Dham ",
      "Rang Ghar",
      "Khaspur"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The upper floor of the temple was actually made of pure gold. It is the holiest place for the Sikh community",
    answer: "Golden Temple",
    options: [
      "Martand Sun Temple",
      "Hadimba Devi Temple",
      "Bajinath Temple",
      "Golden Temple"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "This famous monument in Maharashtra is also called as Dakkhani Taj. Name this monument",
    answer: "Bibi-Ka-Maqbara",
    options: [
      "Bibi-Ka-Maqbara",
      "Agakhan Palace",
      "Morarji Castle",
      "Chand Minar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "This fort was built by Maratha ruler Serfoji II to honour the successful advance of the British over Napoléon Bonaparte. Name this extraordinary fort located in Tamil Nadu",
    answer: "Manora Fort",
    options: [
      "Bekal Fort",
      "Manora Fort",
      "Fort Kochi ",
      "Bidar Fort"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "_______ is one of the biggest churches in north-east India located in Kohima.",
    answer: "Cathollic Church",
    options: [
      "Christ Church",
      "St. Paul Cathedral",
      "Cathollic Church",
      "St. Anne Church"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The Jama Masjid is one of the oldest mosques of the state built in late 16th century by Mughal rulers. In which state is it located?",
    answer: "Jharkhand",
    options: [
      "Odisha",
      "Maharashtra",
      "Telangana",
      "Jharkhand"
    ]
  },
];